Hey, statistically speaking, I'm sure
you have something to worry about.
(Leonard:)What do you mean?
(Sheldon:)Well, if we assume
that your looks are average...
...right off the bat, 50 percent of men on
Earth are more attractive than you.
That's 1.5 billion handsome lads
standing by, waiting to rain on your parade.
(Leonard:)Well, yeah, but this isn't just about looks.
(Leonard:)I'm way above average
in a lot of other things.
(Sheldon:)Not height, vision, athleticism,
or ability to digest dairy products.
(Leonard:)I'm talking about important things
like emotional maturity.
(Sheldon:)You were just spying on your girlfriend
through a peephole.
(Leonard:)I liked it better
when you thought I wasn't here.
(Sheldon:)I'm not saying
you don't have attractive qualities.
(Sheldon:)Your choice of friends is impeccable.
(Sheldon:)You're a good sleeper.
(Sheldon:)And last but not least,
you buy the grapes I like.